<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Adeleke Olorunnisola</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/</link><atom:link href="https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Adeleke Olorunnisola</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2024 Adeleke Olorunnisola</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/media/icon_hub3fcd41eecef6f83a4f1f9ecbf86fc98_380556_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url><title>Adeleke Olorunnisola</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/</link></image><item><title>Example Talk</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/talk/example-talk/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2030 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/talk/example-talk/</guid><description>&lt;div class="alert alert-note">
&lt;div>
Click on the &lt;strong>Slides&lt;/strong> button above to view the built-in slides feature.
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;p>Slides can be added in a few ways:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Create&lt;/strong> slides using Wowchemy&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href="https://wowchemy.com/docs/managing-content/#create-slides" target="_blank" rel="noopener">&lt;em>Slides&lt;/em>&lt;/a> feature and link using &lt;code>slides&lt;/code> parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Upload&lt;/strong> an existing slide deck to &lt;code>static/&lt;/code> and link using &lt;code>url_slides&lt;/code> parameter in the front matter of the talk file&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Embed&lt;/strong> your slides (e.g. Google Slides) or presentation video on this page using &lt;a href="https://wowchemy.com/docs/writing-markdown-latex/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">shortcodes&lt;/a>.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Further event details, including &lt;a href="https://wowchemy.com/docs/writing-markdown-latex/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">page elements&lt;/a> such as image galleries, can be added to the body of this page.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A case study on raw material management in a manufacturing industry using advanced nonlinear optimization technique(NLOT)</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/raw_material_ga/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/raw_material_ga/</guid><description>&lt;p>This study focuses on Raw Material Inventory Optimization for Benmist Water Company in Akure, Nigeria. The goal is to minimize total costs related to raw material holding and ordering, considering demand, holding costs, and ordering costs over a specified time period. Decision variables include order quantity, with parameters like demand, holding cost, ordering cost, initial inventory, storage capacity, and time period.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To solve this optimization problem two algorithms are applied: Genetic Algorithm (GA) and Sequential Quadratic Programming with Linear Programming and Equality Constraints (SLPSQP). GA, inspired by evolution principles, iteratively refines solutions to find optimal order quantities while SLPSQP uses a mathematical programming approach, considering constraints.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Separate optimization runs with both algorithms are conducted, comparing their performance in terms of total cost minimization, convergence speed, computational efficiency, and solution quality. Results show that GA excels in exploring diverse solutions, while SLPSQP demonstrates precision with fewer iterations. The comparison provides insights into exploration-exploitation trade-offs.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This research contributes to inventory management by showcasing the applicability and performance of GA and SLPSQP in addressing real-world raw material optimization challenges for a water bottling company. The insights guide practitioners in selecting the most suitable algorithm based on specific optimization objectives and constraints.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Comparative Study on Filters</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/a_filter_study/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/a_filter_study/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project aims to provide a comprehensive comparison of three state estimation algorithms: the Kalman Filter, the Extended Kalman Filter, and the Particle Filter. These algorithms are widely used in various applications for estimating the state of dynamic systems from noisy measurements. The report will delve into the theoretical foundations of each algorithm, detailing their mathematical formulations and underlying principles. Additionally, the implementation of each algorithm will be discussed, highlighting the key steps and considerations involved. Performance evaluation will be conducted through simulations, where the algorithms will be applied to a common dynamic system model. Metrics such as estimation accuracy, computational efficiency, and robustness to noise will be used to compare the algorithms. The findings from this project will provide valuable insights into the strengths and limitations of each algorithm, guiding practitioners in selecting the appropriate state estimation technique for their specific applications.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Study on Visual Odometry</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/visual_odometry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/visual_odometry/</guid><description>&lt;p>Visual Odometry (VO) is the process of estimating a robot’s position and orientation by analyzing sequential images captured by its on-board cameras. It is a crucial technique in robotics, computer vision and autonomous navigation, as it enables motion tracking without relying on external references like GPS. This project aims to study various processes involved in VO and document the result obtained after implementation of monocular VO using python programming language (simulation environment).&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Conceptual Design of a Shredder for Waste Management</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/plastic_shredder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/plastic_shredder/</guid><description>&lt;p>TThis project involves the conceptual design of a shredder for waste management. It focuses solely on creating a practical and efficient design, detailing component selection, blade configuration, and structural layout. The project emphasizes accurate design measurements and specifications without incorporating analysis, simulations, or prototyping. The goal is to outline a clear and functional design concept suitable for future development.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Design of an Office Ergonomic Table</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/ergonomic_table/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/ergonomic_table/</guid><description>&lt;h4 id="innovative-design-rooted-in-anthropometric-precision">Innovative Design Rooted in Anthropometric Precision&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>At the core of our ergonomic office table design lies a commitment to fostering comfort, productivity, and wellness for users. By incorporating anthropometric data, we’ve engineered a workspace solution that aligns with human physical dimensions, enhancing both functionality and comfort. This approach ensures that our design is not just stylish, but also grounded in precise, user-focused metrics to promote optimal postural health and reduce fatigue during prolonged use.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="understanding-anthropometrics-a-human-centered-approach">Understanding Anthropometrics: A Human-Centered Approach&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Anthropometrics, the study of human body measurements, plays a pivotal role in creating ergonomic products that fit naturally with the body’s movements and dimensions. For this design, extensive research was conducted to assess various anthropometric data points, such as seated elbow height, reach distance, and leg clearance, ensuring our office table can accommodate a wide range of body types and heights. These measurements influence the table’s height, width, depth, and tilt options, providing users with a customizable, adaptable workspace that meets diverse ergonomic needs.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="key-features-and-technical-specifications">Key Features and Technical Specifications&lt;/h4>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Adjustable Height and Angles: Our office table is engineered with flexibility in mind. By allowing users to adjust the table height and surface angle, we enable postural versatility, reducing strain on muscles and joints.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Enhanced Leg Clearance and Knee Room: Derived from precise anthropometric calculations, our design ensures ample space for leg movement and comfort, accommodating various seating preferences.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Optimized Work Surface Depth: The table’s depth is tailored to promote a natural arm extension range, reducing the need to overreach and maintaining a healthy shoulder posture.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Durability and Sustainability: Built from high-quality materials, our table balances ergonomics with sustainability, offering long-lasting durability without compromising environmental considerations.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h4 id="why-ergonomics-matter-in-todays-work-environment">Why Ergonomics Matter in Today’s Work Environment&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>As work environments increasingly demand prolonged sitting hours, ergonomic solutions are crucial for mitigating the risk of strain injuries and enhancing productivity. Our office table, designed through a meticulous application of anthropometric data, embodies this philosophy, providing users with a workspace that supports both physical well-being and productivity.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Meta-Heuristic Optimization Algorithms Based PID Controller Design For A 5-DOF Robotic Manipulator</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/manipulator_pid_optimization/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/manipulator_pid_optimization/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="abstract">Abstract&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>This research presents a comprehensive approach to the design and implementation of a Proportional Integral Derivative (PID) controller for a 5-degree-of-freedom (DOF) robotic manipulator, utilizing meta-heuristic optimization algorithms. The robotic arm, initially designed using SolidWorks, was translated into a Simscape model for simulation purposes. Two distinct optimization algorithms, the Genetic Algorithm (GA) and Ant Colony Optimization&lt;/p>
&lt;p>(ACO), were employed to fine-tune the PID controller gains, aiming to enhance the system’s dynamic performance and stability. The optimized PID gains obtained from simulations were then applied to a physical prototype of the robotic manipulator, which was 3D printed based on the SolidWorks design. The coding and real-time implementation of the PID controllers were conducted using MATLAB.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="problem-statement">Problem statement&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The optimization of the PID controller using Genetic Algorithms and Ant Colony Optimization aims to address the laborious nature of manual PID tuning method.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>These evolutionary and swarm intelligence-based algorithms offer the potential to efficiently explore the vast parameter space, leading to improved controller performance, robustness, and adaptability. The primary challenge lies in achieving optimal&lt;/p>
&lt;p>PID controller parameters for the 5 DOF robotic arm to ensure precise, responsive, and stable control. While current studies often utilize individual nature-inspired optimization algorithms for tuning PID controllers, there is a gap in the literature regarding a comprehensive comparison of the trade-offs and effectiveness of these algorithms specifically applied to a 5-DOF robotic manipulator. This study aims to fill this gap by providing a detailed comparative analysis, ultimately contributing to the development of more efficient and robust control strategies for robotic systems.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="cost-of-implementation-of-both-algorithms-to-pid-control">Cost of implementation of both algorithms to PID control&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="Convergence_plot.jpg" alt="Convergence Plot for the algorithms">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Upon comparison, it was observed that the Genetic Algorithm (GA) exhibited faster convergence and ran more efficiently than the Ant Colony Optimization (ACO) algorithm.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="more-details-of-the-project-and-results-graphs-are-documented-in-the-report">More details of the project and results (graphs) are documented in the report&lt;/h3></description></item><item><title>Optimization of Quadcopter PID controller gains using Genetic Algorithm and Ant Colony Optimization Algorithm</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/quadcopter_pid_optimization/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/quadcopter_pid_optimization/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project highlights a comparative analysis of Proportional Integral Derivative (PID) controllers, commonly used in robotics due to their simplicity and effectiveness. However, traditional manual tuning methods often fall short in delivering optimal performance for specific tasks. To address this, I implemented computational intelligence by using two meta-heuristic algorithms, Genetic Algorithm (GA) and Ant Colony Optimization (ACO), for tuning PID gains. Through simulation in MATLAB 2023a, I explored how these algorithms enhance PID controller performance specifically for quadcopter control. This study not only demonstrates the efficacy of GA and ACO in PID tuning but also offers valuable insights into their applications in autonomous control systems. The documented results and insights contribute to a deeper understanding of how these algorithms support precision in robotic applications.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Simulateneous Localization and Mapping of a constructed environment using turtlebot3</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/slam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/slam/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project highlights a comparative analysis of Proportional Integral Derivative (PID) controllers, commonly used in robotics due to their simplicity and effectiveness. However, traditional manual tuning methods often fall short in delivering optimal performance for specific tasks. To address this, I implemented computational intelligence by using two meta-heuristic algorithms, Genetic Algorithm (GA) and Ant Colony Optimization (ACO), for tuning PID gains. Through simulation in MATLAB 2023a, I explored how these algorithms enhance PID controller performance specifically for quadcopter control. This study not only demonstrates the efficacy of GA and ACO in PID tuning but also offers valuable insights into their applications in autonomous control systems. The documented results and insights contribute to a deeper understanding of how these algorithms support precision in robotic applications.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Trajectory Tracking and Kinematic Control of a Mobile Robot Using Bicycle Model</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/bicycle_model/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/bicycle_model/</guid><description>&lt;h4 id="project-motivation">Project motivation&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>This project focuses on the trajectory tracking and kinematic control of a differential drive mobile robot using the bicycle model. Differential drive robots, known for their simplicity and maneuverability, are commonly used in various autonomous applications, and accurate trajectory tracking is critical for their performance in navigation tasks. The main objective of this project is to implement a trajectory tracking system that uses the bicycle model to simulate and control the movement of a differential drive mobile robot. The system aims to minimize the error between the robot’s current position and the desired path using feedback mechanisms for both velocity and steering control.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="Model.jpg" alt="Contol architecture used">&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="more-details-are-in-the-report">More details are in the report&lt;/h3></description></item><item><title>Slides</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/slides/example/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/slides/example/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="create-slides-in-markdown-with-wowchemy">Create slides in Markdown with Wowchemy&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://wowchemy.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Wowchemy&lt;/a> | &lt;a href="https://owchemy.com/docs/managing-content/#create-slides" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Documentation&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="features">Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Efficiently write slides in Markdown&lt;/li>
&lt;li>3-in-1: Create, Present, and Publish your slides&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Supports speaker notes&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Mobile friendly slides&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="controls">Controls&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Next: &lt;code>Right Arrow&lt;/code> or &lt;code>Space&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Previous: &lt;code>Left Arrow&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Start: &lt;code>Home&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Finish: &lt;code>End&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Overview: &lt;code>Esc&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Speaker notes: &lt;code>S&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Fullscreen: &lt;code>F&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Zoom: &lt;code>Alt + Click&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;a href="https://github.com/hakimel/reveal.js#pdf-export" target="_blank" rel="noopener">PDF Export&lt;/a>: &lt;code>E&lt;/code>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="code-highlighting">Code Highlighting&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Inline code: &lt;code>variable&lt;/code>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Code block:&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code class="language-python">porridge = &amp;quot;blueberry&amp;quot;
if porridge == &amp;quot;blueberry&amp;quot;:
print(&amp;quot;Eating...&amp;quot;)
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="math">Math&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In-line math: $x + y = z$&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Block math:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>$$
f\left( x \right) = ;\frac{{2\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x - 4} \right)}}{{\left( {x + 4} \right)\left( {x + 1} \right)}}
$$&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="fragments">Fragments&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Make content appear incrementally&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code>{{% fragment %}} One {{% /fragment %}}
{{% fragment %}} **Two** {{% /fragment %}}
{{% fragment %}} Three {{% /fragment %}}
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;p>Press &lt;code>Space&lt;/code> to play!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;span class="fragment " >
One
&lt;/span>
&lt;span class="fragment " >
&lt;strong>Two&lt;/strong>
&lt;/span>
&lt;span class="fragment " >
Three
&lt;/span>&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>A fragment can accept two optional parameters:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;code>class&lt;/code>: use a custom style (requires definition in custom CSS)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;code>weight&lt;/code>: sets the order in which a fragment appears&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="speaker-notes">Speaker Notes&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Add speaker notes to your presentation&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code class="language-markdown">{{% speaker_note %}}
- Only the speaker can read these notes
- Press `S` key to view
{{% /speaker_note %}}
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;p>Press the &lt;code>S&lt;/code> key to view the speaker notes!&lt;/p>
&lt;aside class="notes">
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Only the speaker can read these notes&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Press &lt;code>S&lt;/code> key to view&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/aside>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="themes">Themes&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>black: Black background, white text, blue links (default)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>white: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li>
&lt;li>league: Gray background, white text, blue links&lt;/li>
&lt;li>beige: Beige background, dark text, brown links&lt;/li>
&lt;li>sky: Blue background, thin dark text, blue links&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>night: Black background, thick white text, orange links&lt;/li>
&lt;li>serif: Cappuccino background, gray text, brown links&lt;/li>
&lt;li>simple: White background, black text, blue links&lt;/li>
&lt;li>solarized: Cream-colored background, dark green text, blue links&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;hr>
&lt;section data-noprocess data-shortcode-slide
data-background-image="/media/boards.jpg"
>
&lt;h2 id="custom-slide">Custom Slide&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Customize the slide style and background&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code class="language-markdown">{{&amp;lt; slide background-image=&amp;quot;/media/boards.jpg&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
{{&amp;lt; slide background-color=&amp;quot;#0000FF&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
{{&amp;lt; slide class=&amp;quot;my-style&amp;quot; &amp;gt;}}
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h2 id="custom-css-example">Custom CSS Example&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Let&amp;rsquo;s make headers navy colored.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Create &lt;code>assets/css/reveal_custom.css&lt;/code> with:&lt;/p>
&lt;pre>&lt;code class="language-css">.reveal section h1,
.reveal section h2,
.reveal section h3 {
color: navy;
}
&lt;/code>&lt;/pre>
&lt;hr>
&lt;h1 id="questions">Questions?&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://github.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-modules/discussions" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Ask&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://wowchemy.com/docs/managing-content/#create-slides" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Documentation&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>My Projects</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/allprojects/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/allprojects/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/admin/config.yml</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/admin/config.yml</guid><description/></item><item><title>Development and Performance Evaluation of a Quadcopter</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/publication/development_of_quadcopter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/publication/development_of_quadcopter/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Material Defect Detection using Deep Learning Architectures for Quality Control</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/material_defect_detection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/material_defect_detection/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="problem-statement">Problem statement&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Ensuring precise detection of surface defects in materials is crucial for maintaining quality standards. This project aims to evaluate and compare deep learning models to identify the most effective approach for defect detection, ultimately enhancing quality control processes.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="more-details-of-the-project-and-results-are-documented-in-the-slide">More details of the project and results are documented in the slide&lt;/h3></description></item><item><title>Model Predictive Control for Advanced Path Tracking and Stabilization in Autonomous Mobile Robots Using Linearized Kinematic and Dynamic Models</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/publication/model_predictive_control/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/publication/model_predictive_control/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Optimization of Quadcopter PID Controller Gains using Ant Colony Optimization and Genetic Algorithm</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/publication/quadcopter_pid_control/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/publication/quadcopter_pid_control/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Smart Manufacturing and its Impact on Production Processes : A Review</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/publication/smart_manufacturing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/publication/smart_manufacturing/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>