<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Robotics | Adeleke Olorunnisola</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/tag/robotics/</link><atom:link href="https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/tag/robotics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Robotics</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2024 Adeleke Olorunnisola</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/media/icon_hub3fcd41eecef6f83a4f1f9ecbf86fc98_380556_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url><title>Robotics</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/tag/robotics/</link></image><item><title>Meta-Heuristic Optimization Algorithms Based PID Controller Design For A 5-DOF Robotic Manipulator</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/manipulator_pid_optimization/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/manipulator_pid_optimization/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="abstract">Abstract&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>This research presents a comprehensive approach to the design and implementation of a Proportional Integral Derivative (PID) controller for a 5-degree-of-freedom (DOF) robotic manipulator, utilizing meta-heuristic optimization algorithms. The robotic arm, initially designed using SolidWorks, was translated into a Simscape model for simulation purposes. Two distinct optimization algorithms, the Genetic Algorithm (GA) and Ant Colony Optimization&lt;/p>
&lt;p>(ACO), were employed to fine-tune the PID controller gains, aiming to enhance the system’s dynamic performance and stability. The optimized PID gains obtained from simulations were then applied to a physical prototype of the robotic manipulator, which was 3D printed based on the SolidWorks design. The coding and real-time implementation of the PID controllers were conducted using MATLAB.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="problem-statement">Problem statement&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The optimization of the PID controller using Genetic Algorithms and Ant Colony Optimization aims to address the laborious nature of manual PID tuning method.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>These evolutionary and swarm intelligence-based algorithms offer the potential to efficiently explore the vast parameter space, leading to improved controller performance, robustness, and adaptability. The primary challenge lies in achieving optimal&lt;/p>
&lt;p>PID controller parameters for the 5 DOF robotic arm to ensure precise, responsive, and stable control. While current studies often utilize individual nature-inspired optimization algorithms for tuning PID controllers, there is a gap in the literature regarding a comprehensive comparison of the trade-offs and effectiveness of these algorithms specifically applied to a 5-DOF robotic manipulator. This study aims to fill this gap by providing a detailed comparative analysis, ultimately contributing to the development of more efficient and robust control strategies for robotic systems.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="cost-of-implementation-of-both-algorithms-to-pid-control">Cost of implementation of both algorithms to PID control&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="Convergence_plot.jpg" alt="Convergence Plot for the algorithms">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Upon comparison, it was observed that the Genetic Algorithm (GA) exhibited faster convergence and ran more efficiently than the Ant Colony Optimization (ACO) algorithm.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="more-details-of-the-project-and-results-graphs-are-documented-in-the-report">More details of the project and results (graphs) are documented in the report&lt;/h3></description></item><item><title>Optimization of Quadcopter PID controller gains using Genetic Algorithm and Ant Colony Optimization Algorithm</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/quadcopter_pid_optimization/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/quadcopter_pid_optimization/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project highlights a comparative analysis of Proportional Integral Derivative (PID) controllers, commonly used in robotics due to their simplicity and effectiveness. However, traditional manual tuning methods often fall short in delivering optimal performance for specific tasks. To address this, I implemented computational intelligence by using two meta-heuristic algorithms, Genetic Algorithm (GA) and Ant Colony Optimization (ACO), for tuning PID gains. Through simulation in MATLAB 2023a, I explored how these algorithms enhance PID controller performance specifically for quadcopter control. This study not only demonstrates the efficacy of GA and ACO in PID tuning but also offers valuable insights into their applications in autonomous control systems. The documented results and insights contribute to a deeper understanding of how these algorithms support precision in robotic applications.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Simulateneous Localization and Mapping of a constructed environment using turtlebot3</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/slam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/slam/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project highlights a comparative analysis of Proportional Integral Derivative (PID) controllers, commonly used in robotics due to their simplicity and effectiveness. However, traditional manual tuning methods often fall short in delivering optimal performance for specific tasks. To address this, I implemented computational intelligence by using two meta-heuristic algorithms, Genetic Algorithm (GA) and Ant Colony Optimization (ACO), for tuning PID gains. Through simulation in MATLAB 2023a, I explored how these algorithms enhance PID controller performance specifically for quadcopter control. This study not only demonstrates the efficacy of GA and ACO in PID tuning but also offers valuable insights into their applications in autonomous control systems. The documented results and insights contribute to a deeper understanding of how these algorithms support precision in robotic applications.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Trajectory Tracking and Kinematic Control of a Mobile Robot Using Bicycle Model</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/bicycle_model/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/bicycle_model/</guid><description>&lt;h4 id="project-motivation">Project motivation&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>This project focuses on the trajectory tracking and kinematic control of a differential drive mobile robot using the bicycle model. Differential drive robots, known for their simplicity and maneuverability, are commonly used in various autonomous applications, and accurate trajectory tracking is critical for their performance in navigation tasks. The main objective of this project is to implement a trajectory tracking system that uses the bicycle model to simulate and control the movement of a differential drive mobile robot. The system aims to minimize the error between the robot’s current position and the desired path using feedback mechanisms for both velocity and steering control.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="Model.jpg" alt="Contol architecture used">&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="more-details-are-in-the-report">More details are in the report&lt;/h3></description></item><item><title>Material Defect Detection using Deep Learning Architectures for Quality Control</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/material_defect_detection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/material_defect_detection/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="problem-statement">Problem statement&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Ensuring precise detection of surface defects in materials is crucial for maintaining quality standards. This project aims to evaluate and compare deep learning models to identify the most effective approach for defect detection, ultimately enhancing quality control processes.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="more-details-of-the-project-and-results-are-documented-in-the-slide">More details of the project and results are documented in the slide&lt;/h3></description></item></channel></rss>