<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Robotics and Automation | Adeleke Olorunnisola</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/tag/robotics-and-automation/</link><atom:link href="https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/tag/robotics-and-automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Robotics and Automation</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2024 Adeleke Olorunnisola</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/media/icon_hub3fcd41eecef6f83a4f1f9ecbf86fc98_380556_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url><title>Robotics and Automation</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/tag/robotics-and-automation/</link></image><item><title>A Comparative Study on Filters</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/a_filter_study/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/a_filter_study/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project aims to provide a comprehensive comparison of three state estimation algorithms: the Kalman Filter, the Extended Kalman Filter, and the Particle Filter. These algorithms are widely used in various applications for estimating the state of dynamic systems from noisy measurements. The report will delve into the theoretical foundations of each algorithm, detailing their mathematical formulations and underlying principles. Additionally, the implementation of each algorithm will be discussed, highlighting the key steps and considerations involved. Performance evaluation will be conducted through simulations, where the algorithms will be applied to a common dynamic system model. Metrics such as estimation accuracy, computational efficiency, and robustness to noise will be used to compare the algorithms. The findings from this project will provide valuable insights into the strengths and limitations of each algorithm, guiding practitioners in selecting the appropriate state estimation technique for their specific applications.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Study on Visual Odometry</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/visual_odometry/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/visual_odometry/</guid><description>&lt;p>Visual Odometry (VO) is the process of estimating a robot’s position and orientation by analyzing sequential images captured by its on-board cameras. It is a crucial technique in robotics, computer vision and autonomous navigation, as it enables motion tracking without relying on external references like GPS. This project aims to study various processes involved in VO and document the result obtained after implementation of monocular VO using python programming language (simulation environment).&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>