<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Optimization | Adeleke Olorunnisola</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/tag/optimization/</link><atom:link href="https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/tag/optimization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Optimization</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2024 Adeleke Olorunnisola</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/media/icon_hub3fcd41eecef6f83a4f1f9ecbf86fc98_380556_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url><title>Optimization</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/tag/optimization/</link></image><item><title>A case study on raw material management in a manufacturing industry using advanced nonlinear optimization technique(NLOT)</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/raw_material_ga/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/raw_material_ga/</guid><description>&lt;p>This study focuses on Raw Material Inventory Optimization for Benmist Water Company in Akure, Nigeria. The goal is to minimize total costs related to raw material holding and ordering, considering demand, holding costs, and ordering costs over a specified time period. Decision variables include order quantity, with parameters like demand, holding cost, ordering cost, initial inventory, storage capacity, and time period.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To solve this optimization problem two algorithms are applied: Genetic Algorithm (GA) and Sequential Quadratic Programming with Linear Programming and Equality Constraints (SLPSQP). GA, inspired by evolution principles, iteratively refines solutions to find optimal order quantities while SLPSQP uses a mathematical programming approach, considering constraints.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Separate optimization runs with both algorithms are conducted, comparing their performance in terms of total cost minimization, convergence speed, computational efficiency, and solution quality. Results show that GA excels in exploring diverse solutions, while SLPSQP demonstrates precision with fewer iterations. The comparison provides insights into exploration-exploitation trade-offs.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This research contributes to inventory management by showcasing the applicability and performance of GA and SLPSQP in addressing real-world raw material optimization challenges for a water bottling company. The insights guide practitioners in selecting the most suitable algorithm based on specific optimization objectives and constraints.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Conceptual Design of a Shredder for Waste Management</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/plastic_shredder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/plastic_shredder/</guid><description>&lt;p>TThis project involves the conceptual design of a shredder for waste management. It focuses solely on creating a practical and efficient design, detailing component selection, blade configuration, and structural layout. The project emphasizes accurate design measurements and specifications without incorporating analysis, simulations, or prototyping. The goal is to outline a clear and functional design concept suitable for future development.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Meta-Heuristic Optimization Algorithms Based PID Controller Design For A 5-DOF Robotic Manipulator</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/manipulator_pid_optimization/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/manipulator_pid_optimization/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="abstract">Abstract&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>This research presents a comprehensive approach to the design and implementation of a Proportional Integral Derivative (PID) controller for a 5-degree-of-freedom (DOF) robotic manipulator, utilizing meta-heuristic optimization algorithms. The robotic arm, initially designed using SolidWorks, was translated into a Simscape model for simulation purposes. Two distinct optimization algorithms, the Genetic Algorithm (GA) and Ant Colony Optimization&lt;/p>
&lt;p>(ACO), were employed to fine-tune the PID controller gains, aiming to enhance the system’s dynamic performance and stability. The optimized PID gains obtained from simulations were then applied to a physical prototype of the robotic manipulator, which was 3D printed based on the SolidWorks design. The coding and real-time implementation of the PID controllers were conducted using MATLAB.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="problem-statement">Problem statement&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The optimization of the PID controller using Genetic Algorithms and Ant Colony Optimization aims to address the laborious nature of manual PID tuning method.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>These evolutionary and swarm intelligence-based algorithms offer the potential to efficiently explore the vast parameter space, leading to improved controller performance, robustness, and adaptability. The primary challenge lies in achieving optimal&lt;/p>
&lt;p>PID controller parameters for the 5 DOF robotic arm to ensure precise, responsive, and stable control. While current studies often utilize individual nature-inspired optimization algorithms for tuning PID controllers, there is a gap in the literature regarding a comprehensive comparison of the trade-offs and effectiveness of these algorithms specifically applied to a 5-DOF robotic manipulator. This study aims to fill this gap by providing a detailed comparative analysis, ultimately contributing to the development of more efficient and robust control strategies for robotic systems.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="cost-of-implementation-of-both-algorithms-to-pid-control">Cost of implementation of both algorithms to PID control&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="Convergence_plot.jpg" alt="Convergence Plot for the algorithms">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Upon comparison, it was observed that the Genetic Algorithm (GA) exhibited faster convergence and ran more efficiently than the Ant Colony Optimization (ACO) algorithm.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="more-details-of-the-project-and-results-graphs-are-documented-in-the-report">More details of the project and results (graphs) are documented in the report&lt;/h3></description></item><item><title>Optimization of Quadcopter PID controller gains using Genetic Algorithm and Ant Colony Optimization Algorithm</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/quadcopter_pid_optimization/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/quadcopter_pid_optimization/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project highlights a comparative analysis of Proportional Integral Derivative (PID) controllers, commonly used in robotics due to their simplicity and effectiveness. However, traditional manual tuning methods often fall short in delivering optimal performance for specific tasks. To address this, I implemented computational intelligence by using two meta-heuristic algorithms, Genetic Algorithm (GA) and Ant Colony Optimization (ACO), for tuning PID gains. Through simulation in MATLAB 2023a, I explored how these algorithms enhance PID controller performance specifically for quadcopter control. This study not only demonstrates the efficacy of GA and ACO in PID tuning but also offers valuable insights into their applications in autonomous control systems. The documented results and insights contribute to a deeper understanding of how these algorithms support precision in robotic applications.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>