<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Smart manufacturing | Adeleke Olorunnisola</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/tag/smart-manufacturing/</link><atom:link href="https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/tag/smart-manufacturing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Smart manufacturing</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2024 Adeleke Olorunnisola</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/media/icon_hub3fcd41eecef6f83a4f1f9ecbf86fc98_380556_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url><title>Smart manufacturing</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/tag/smart-manufacturing/</link></image><item><title>A case study on raw material management in a manufacturing industry using advanced nonlinear optimization technique(NLOT)</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/raw_material_ga/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/raw_material_ga/</guid><description>&lt;p>This study focuses on Raw Material Inventory Optimization for Benmist Water Company in Akure, Nigeria. The goal is to minimize total costs related to raw material holding and ordering, considering demand, holding costs, and ordering costs over a specified time period. Decision variables include order quantity, with parameters like demand, holding cost, ordering cost, initial inventory, storage capacity, and time period.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To solve this optimization problem two algorithms are applied: Genetic Algorithm (GA) and Sequential Quadratic Programming with Linear Programming and Equality Constraints (SLPSQP). GA, inspired by evolution principles, iteratively refines solutions to find optimal order quantities while SLPSQP uses a mathematical programming approach, considering constraints.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Separate optimization runs with both algorithms are conducted, comparing their performance in terms of total cost minimization, convergence speed, computational efficiency, and solution quality. Results show that GA excels in exploring diverse solutions, while SLPSQP demonstrates precision with fewer iterations. The comparison provides insights into exploration-exploitation trade-offs.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This research contributes to inventory management by showcasing the applicability and performance of GA and SLPSQP in addressing real-world raw material optimization challenges for a water bottling company. The insights guide practitioners in selecting the most suitable algorithm based on specific optimization objectives and constraints.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Design of an Office Ergonomic Table</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/ergonomic_table/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/ergonomic_table/</guid><description>&lt;h4 id="innovative-design-rooted-in-anthropometric-precision">Innovative Design Rooted in Anthropometric Precision&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>At the core of our ergonomic office table design lies a commitment to fostering comfort, productivity, and wellness for users. By incorporating anthropometric data, we’ve engineered a workspace solution that aligns with human physical dimensions, enhancing both functionality and comfort. This approach ensures that our design is not just stylish, but also grounded in precise, user-focused metrics to promote optimal postural health and reduce fatigue during prolonged use.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="understanding-anthropometrics-a-human-centered-approach">Understanding Anthropometrics: A Human-Centered Approach&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Anthropometrics, the study of human body measurements, plays a pivotal role in creating ergonomic products that fit naturally with the body’s movements and dimensions. For this design, extensive research was conducted to assess various anthropometric data points, such as seated elbow height, reach distance, and leg clearance, ensuring our office table can accommodate a wide range of body types and heights. These measurements influence the table’s height, width, depth, and tilt options, providing users with a customizable, adaptable workspace that meets diverse ergonomic needs.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="key-features-and-technical-specifications">Key Features and Technical Specifications&lt;/h4>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Adjustable Height and Angles: Our office table is engineered with flexibility in mind. By allowing users to adjust the table height and surface angle, we enable postural versatility, reducing strain on muscles and joints.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Enhanced Leg Clearance and Knee Room: Derived from precise anthropometric calculations, our design ensures ample space for leg movement and comfort, accommodating various seating preferences.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Optimized Work Surface Depth: The table’s depth is tailored to promote a natural arm extension range, reducing the need to overreach and maintaining a healthy shoulder posture.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Durability and Sustainability: Built from high-quality materials, our table balances ergonomics with sustainability, offering long-lasting durability without compromising environmental considerations.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;h4 id="why-ergonomics-matter-in-todays-work-environment">Why Ergonomics Matter in Today’s Work Environment&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>As work environments increasingly demand prolonged sitting hours, ergonomic solutions are crucial for mitigating the risk of strain injuries and enhancing productivity. Our office table, designed through a meticulous application of anthropometric data, embodies this philosophy, providing users with a workspace that supports both physical well-being and productivity.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Simulateneous Localization and Mapping of a constructed environment using turtlebot3</title><link>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/slam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://olorunnisola.netlify.app/project/slam/</guid><description>&lt;p>This project highlights a comparative analysis of Proportional Integral Derivative (PID) controllers, commonly used in robotics due to their simplicity and effectiveness. However, traditional manual tuning methods often fall short in delivering optimal performance for specific tasks. To address this, I implemented computational intelligence by using two meta-heuristic algorithms, Genetic Algorithm (GA) and Ant Colony Optimization (ACO), for tuning PID gains. Through simulation in MATLAB 2023a, I explored how these algorithms enhance PID controller performance specifically for quadcopter control. This study not only demonstrates the efficacy of GA and ACO in PID tuning but also offers valuable insights into their applications in autonomous control systems. The documented results and insights contribute to a deeper understanding of how these algorithms support precision in robotic applications.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>